take away the territory so that there
территорию забрать чтобы натовских баз
are no NATO bases take away what country you were in
не было забрать в какой страна ты был
except your
кроме свой
village except your
виллидж кроме свой
silo I’m in
сило я в
Russia That is, you’ve never been to another
России То есть ты никогда не был другой
country but you want to take another country for
страна но хочешь забрать другой страна
yourself
себе
Hello
Алло
AMM
АММ
Ari I’m from the city of
ари я из город са
America I speak Russian but  bad Okay Oh
амери я говорить по-русски но плохо Окей
what
О какой
city
город
Stavropol shout
Ставрополь кричать
Stavropol
Ставропольский
region Stavropol si
край Ставрополь си
hundred
ста
region how do you feel Ukraine Russia
регион как ты относится Украина Россия
war
война
Normal Normal this is
Нормально Нормально это
how you support
как поддерживаешь
you
ты
fight
воевать
I I we support
я я мы поддерживать
war you fight for Russia against Ukraine
война ты воевать за Росси против Украина
there is
есть й
why why take the territory so that there
зачем зачем территорию забрать чтоб
are no NATO bases to take what
натовских баз не было забрать в какой
country you were in except your village except
страна ты был кроме свой вилидж кроме
your
свой
village in
село я
Russia That is, you have never been to another
России То есть ты никогда не был другой
country but you want to take another country
страна но хочешь забрать другой страна
Why another country in Soviet style  in the USSR there
Почему другой страна по советски по СССР
used to be the
раньше было
USSR It was one big
СССР Это был одна большая
territory and in the Russian Empire Ran
территория и в Российской империи Ran
Yeah there was
Ага был
one Big
одна Биг
country
страна
yes Yes yes yes then they
да Да да да потом они
separated separatists Sepa yes yes yes yes
отделились сепаратисты Сепа да да да да
they separated and became uh
отделились они и стал э
Mika small small small
Мика маленький маленький маленький
small as it will be
маленький как будет
sl sl
сл сл
little Gorbachev
малень Горбачёв
Gorbachev you see
Горбач ты видеть
Gorbachev How old are you TV
Горбачёв Сколько тебе лет телевизор
30 you were born in the
30 ты родился в
USSR in the
СССР в
nineties the
девяностые
car was still with the USSR collapsed in
авто ещ был с ССР развалился в
1990 you don’t remember the USSR you
де 1990 ты не помните СССР ты маленький
were little Yes okay oh and you want to come
был Да окей ой а ты хотеть приехать
America America is a very rich country
Америка Америка очень богатая страна
very very much
очень очень много всего
We also have a lot of everything.
есть у нас тоже очень много всего есть у
We have the North Caucasus, the rich North
нас Северный Кавказ богатый Северный
Caucasus. What does the North Caucasus mean?
Кавказ Что значит Северный
South south of Russia South
Кавказ Юг юг России Юг
south  North or
юг Северный или
south The North Caucasus is in the south of the
юг Северный Кавказ находится на юге
country The
страны
North is not North in the
Северный не Северный на
south
юге
Yes, I don’t understand Russians North top map south
Да русских не понимаю Север верх карта
bottom map like North in the
юг низ карта как Северный на
south we say so North Caucasus
юге у нас так говорят Северный Кавказ
forget the North Caucasus on the
забей Северный Кавказ на
tour yes
туре да
North in the south so is North Caucasus
Северный на юге так е е Северный Кавказ
map Open
карта Открой
map map so
карта карта так
yes Northern
да Северный
Caucasus why is it northern if it is
Кавказ почему он северный если он на
not in the south
юге не
[music] it’s
[музыка]
clear here we
понятно у нас у нас так
say that why are you going to the south You say Northern
говорят зачем вы на юг Говорите Северный
Caucasus Well  because it is between north and
Кавказ Ну потому что он между севером и
south, therefore
югом поэтому
northern if it is located between
Северный если он располагаться между
north and south it is the
севером и югом он
center No it is
центр Нет он
northern you can’t understand if it is between north and
северный не понять если он между Север и
south
Юг
it is
он
northern correctly Zadornov said about
северный правильно Задорнов говорил про
you you don’t understand
вас вы не понимаете
us Zadornov is
нас Задорнов это Президент
your President no
ваш нет
Zadornov Write on the
Задорнов Напиши на
computer who  he's a musician politician
компьютер кто он музыкант политик
Now I'll tell you
Сейчас я тебе
this joker joker joker shoot Jester
этот шутник шутник шутник стрелять Шут
Jester No
Шут Нет
Sniper comedian comedian
Снайпер комик комик
comedian
комик
Komi Perky
коми Задорный
according to you No ha ha ha ha
по ваше сказать Нет ха-ха ха-ха
he
он людей
makes people laugh  Lude people from
веселит людей Люде люди от
him there are no people uh He makes people
него людей нет ээ Он заставляет людей
laugh makes people he is a bandit makes
смеяться заставляет людей он бандит
people no he makes them laugh joke joker
людей нет он смешит их шутка шутник
mix this
смешивать это
laugh no he laugh and
сме нет он смеяться и
made a little
застав чуть-чуть
funny as in English
смеши как по-английски
laugh sme
смешить сме
pos not
пос не
Petrosyan's deputy
Петросяна
russian Zadornov Zadornov ass
руски Задорнов Задорнов зад
Zadornov  Yes there is
Задорнов Да есть
orno Zadornov yes m two words
орно Задорнов да м два слова
Zadornov
Задорнов
and first name ass surname
и имя зад фамилия
orno e e ass orno Zadornov Zadornov And
орно е е зад орно Задорнов Задорнов А
this is no ass orno Zadornov  one one
это нет зад орно Задорнов одно одно
word e e e Yes e
слово е е е Yes е
o He
о Он
died is Yeah I thought it’s now you have
умер есть Ага я думал это сейчас у вас
it no in
он есть нет в
2019 he died and he
2019 умер а он людей
made people laugh so there is a Russian joke laughter
смешил так есть русский шутка смех
prolong
продлевать
life No he prolongs the life of others but
жизнь Нет он продлевать другим жизнь а
like
сам лайк
like like
лайк
that yes
это да
And you watch  cheerfully
А ты смотреть задорно
Always almost
Всегда почти
What do you remember tell some kind of joke
А что ты помнишь скажи какой-то шутка
Zadornov Now now yes I’ll remember so
Задорнова Сейчас сейчас да вспомню так
Americans
американцы
really look look look Wait
реально смотри смотри смотри Подожди
wait wait I
подожди подожди
remembered  2 + 2 y
вспомнил 2 + 2 у
2 how much will be 2 P 2 y 2 how much
2 сколько будет 2 П 2 у 2 сколько
will be And
буде А
your How to say scientist I say
ваш Как сказать учёный говорю
what our scientist is
вово какой наш учёный
Well, he was with you in America and says
Ну он был у вас в Америке и говорит то
what your scientist said to eight of our scientists and
что ваш учёный сказал восем наш учёный и
checked Yes, and checked on a calculator and
проверял Да и проверял на калькуляторе а
calculator  gave the answer
калькулятор дал ответ
vo What is a
вос Что такое
calculator you enter it he himself counts
калькулятор забиваешь он сам считает
counts the numbers let's say 2 P 2 yes the
считает числа допустим 2 П 2 да
computer yes the
компьютер да
computer and he gave the answer then he
компьютер и он дал ответ во потом он
entered the computer a second time and it gave the
забил компьютер второй раз и тот дал
answer six
ответ шесть
si si  and they argued there would be eight or
си си и они спорили будет восемь или
six and that needed both a psychoanalyst
шесть а тому Понадобился и психоаналитик
and a computer at the same time. It’s cool and
одновременно и компьютер Прикольно а у
we have
нас есть
uh the president ex-president Barack Obama
ээ президент экс-президент Барак Обама
you know
знаешь
this one you don’t have one you don’t have this one what’s his name
такой у вас его нет у вас этот как его
who fell the
который упал
president of the bar
президент бара
Obama he has such a joke Russian no
Обама у него есть такая шутка русский не
know what 7 mind is How much will it be 7
знать что такое 7 ум На сколько будет 7
Smartly by
Умно на
8 56
8 56
multiplication
умножени таблица
multiplication table multiplication table What is the
умножения таблица умножения Что такое
multiplication table Well this is
умножения Ну это
sowing D 6 ZhD here
сево Д 6 ЖД вот
semu
семю
family no
семья нет
j
дж
twice d That's what
дважды д Вот что такое
twice I'm bad Russian j 6 -
дважды я плохо русски дж 6 -
it's like two two two twice two zna two
это как два два два дважды два зна два
zna two
зна два
twice 2 2 4 2 6
дважды 2 2 4 2 6
12 E what is
12 Э что такое
twice it's like 2 y on 2 a multiplication
дважды это как 2 у на 2 а multiplication
2 y 2 o  twice no 3 y 3 thrice
2 у 2 о дважды нет 3 у 3 трижды
ok ok ok 4 y
окей окей окей 4 у
4 4 4 16 a 5 y
4 4 4 16 а 5 у
5 25 how is this
5 25 а как это
5D
5Д
you
ты
times
раз
its twice op it's
сво это дважды оп это
pdp three three times four Four times p five
пдп три трижды четыре Четырежды п пять
wait
жды
p
п
[music]
[музыка]
p you're there listening to movie music
п ты там слушать музыка кино Ну
Well, you live in the village You have Animals
ну а ты жить в селе У тебя есть Animals
uh
ээ
animals are oh Uh what
животные есть ой Ээ какие
uh dog and Kat Kat uh animals there
ээ дог и Кэт Кэт а ээ животные там
uh  chicken e Cow
ээ курица э Корова
And now I’ll tell you
А сейчас я тебе скажу
for you
для тебя
This is a
Этот это крыса
rat rat we eat it we
крыса мы её кушаем мы её
eat it It’s
кушаем Она
delicious you can show me this
вкусная можешь показать мне этот
Chris Udo go out to
Криса Удо на у выходить
eat Meat  nutri it's delicious can
кушать Мясо нутри это вкусно может
Show the meat
Покажи мясо
nutri you eat
нутри ты кушать
Chris
Криса
Yes Impossible
Yes Impossible
[music]
[музыка]
you eat raw
ты кушать сырой
meat this is a samovar the Russian samovar was yes
мясо это самовар русский самовар был да
electric show I always want to
электрический покажи я всегда хотеть
see the Tula
посмотреть Тульский
samovar
самовар
Wow and what is the middle you can show
Вау а что середина можешь показать
e
е
Al electrics not firewood Not firewood Don't eat
Аль электрика не дрова Не дрова Не есть
and Wood-burning  but it's in a barn in a barn barn
и Дровяной но он в сарае в сарай сарай
barn - this is a bar
сарай - это Бар
barn this is a separate room where it
барн е это отдельное помещение где
is stored Well, different  things, that is,
хранится Ну разные вещи то есть
tools Yeah Okay tool Oke
инструменты Ага Окей инструмент Оке
va And the Ukrainians also tell me that the
ва А ещё мне украинцы говорит что у
Russians don’t have toilets, that’s
русских нет унитазы это
true
правда
Well
Ну
can y and it’s pressed or this is a model of
can у а он нажимается или это макет
the toilet it’s pressed Well, do you have
унитаза это нажимается Ну у вас есть
water or is it just a toilet and then
вода или это просто унитаз а потом
take it out there and press Show how  it
выносите есть а нажми Покажи как оно
is drained so that I can see How to
сливать чтобы я увидел Как
drain the water show me
сливать вода покажи
now
сечас
press yes work for me today the
нажимать да работать мне сегодня
Ukrainian girl says that the Russians
украинский девушка говорит что у русских
do not have toilets, they are taking the toilet from Ukraine
нет унитазы они забирать из Украины
it's
унитаз это
true It's a TV plasma
правда Это телевизор плазма
e inte Internet
е инте интернет
Internet you have Internet at home Yes
интернет у тебя дома есть Интернет Есть
Wow,
Вау
there's such a thing in My city, it's a very
же вот такой вот есть в Мой город очень
expensive house, the Internet is the
дорого дом интернет
only one that's
только
mine and it's gold
мой это и золото
to look for a metal detector wow wow
искать металлодетектор вау вау
you're robbing a
ты грабить
bank
банк
Well, deputy Kul himself Why do you need to look
Ну зам сам Кул А зачем тебе Ну ты искать
gold you are looking for someone else's Money and take
золото ты ищешь чужой Мани и забирать
money Yes, we do this This is in Russia That
мани Да мы так делаем Это в России То
is, you find gold gold then
есть ты находишь золото золото то
gold is Mr. thing Like a pawnshop pawnshop
золото есть мр штука Как ломбард ломбард
ok oh you  bring gold to you give
а окей о ты приносить золото тебе давать
money there e e e ok and a lot so you
деньги есть е е е о'кей и много так
can get
можно получить
money per gram for 1 g 1 Gra Well gram 1
денег за грамм за 1 г 1 Гра Ну грам 1
g they give 5,000 rubles 5,000 5,000 in dollars
г дают 5.000 руб 5.000 5000 в долларах
how much is
сколько
it now I’ll
это сейчас тебе
tell you a dollar now How much is 80 with us it’s
скажу доллар сейчас Почём 80 у нас это
70 dollars  70 dollars 70 dollars
70 долларов 70 долла 70 долларов
60 Well
60 Ну
6 56 You said 7 to 8 60 62 dollars
6 56 Ты же говорил 7 на 8 60 62 доллара
61 Well  yes 61 like that And where do you
61 Ну да 61 вот так примерно А где ты
dig this
копать это
gold in the fields by the sea
золото в полях на море
you have gold growing in the
у вас растёт золото в
fields no in the ground lying in the ground
полях нет в земле валяется в земле
from where Who put the gold in the
откуда Кто положил золото в
field you understand before there was Tsarist
поле понимаешь раньше была Царская
Russia
Россия
Rape someone walked let’s say and lost
рапе кто-нибудь шёл допустим и потерял
the gold lost Yeah well  fell fell lost
золото потерял Ага ну упало выпало
lost coins that
потерял монеты то
is fell fell out and you found it and sold it
есть упали выпали и ты его нашл и продал
or someone lost it at sea That is, while
или на море кто-нибудь потерял То есть
swimming it flew off your hand or from a chain
купался оно слетело с руки или с цепочка
and lost And we find it Well, it’s you
и потерял А мы находить Ну это его Ты
must if you find You must give it to
должен если находить Ты должен отдать у
us in America EU if you found someone else's
нас в Америка ес если ты нашёл чужое
ring or someone else's chain you must
кольцо или чужой цепочка ты обязан
give it
отдать
to the authorities to give it and the power to find it Whose is
го власти отдать а власть найти тот Чья
this your
ва это твой
collection this is not
коллекция это не
gold these are
золото это
coins Soviet
монеты советские
coins And this is not interesting Soviet if
монеты А это не интересно советские если
old coins
давние монеты
there Empire Roman
там Empire римские
Empire is also expensive this
Империя тоже дорогие этом
[music]
[музыка]
Well 200 dollars Wow what kind of
Ну 200 долларов Вау что это за
coin is 5
монета 5
kopecks 200 dollars 5
коп 200 долларов 5
kopecks there is a Soviet tip 5 kopecks  200
коп есть совет советских 5 коп 200
dollars
долларов
there they are rare they are rare rare here from
есть они редкие они редкие редки вот из
rare R Chervony red
редки R Червоный красный
No they are rare That is
Нет они мало встречаются То есть
why they are rare And what do you
их Поэтому они редкие А кем ты
work as an
работать
electrician
электрик
Okay You do it yourself at home as an electrician, there is a
Окей Ты сам у себя дома делать электрика
work at a factory, a school,
есть а работать завод школа
which is what your factory does,
какой вот а что делает твой завод
uh  I saw big supports like this,
ээ а видел большие такие опоры п опоры
supports like this, along which the wires go
опоры такие по которым провода идут
so thick and a
такие толстые та а столб
pole, a pole, yes, they’re big, uh, so we climb on them
столб Да большие такие э вот мы по ним
and throw
лазим и кидаем
wires, cable, we’re climbing here
провода кабель ла лазим вот
we climb Well
лазим Ну
up to the top
наверх наверх
about
о
karaka and we throw and
карака да и кидаем и
throw eat climbed and threw and so that he was in the
кидаем есть залез и кинул а чтобы был в
houses I
домах понял
understood I understood this is a very very important job Yes
понял это очень очень важная работа Да
and you you fight Ukraine or someone
а ты ты воевать Украина или кто-то у
from your father brother fight ukra
тебя из отец брат воевать укра
uncle
дядя
Ankle uncle uncle uncle he  alive
Анкл дядя дядя дядя он живой
wounded alive And where is he fighting Ukraine
раненный живой А где он воюет Украина
Russia
Россия
where is
где
Ukraine there is a lot of Ukraine Russia is
Украина там много Украина Россия
fighting I'm in
воюет Я в
Ukraine I'm hmm
Украине я хму
Bah there and Odessa there's war
Бах там а Одесса там война
Odessa Odessa Yes he's in  Morkah
Одесса Одесса Да он в морках
and
а
oh Moscow you know the cruiser Moscow
ой Москва знаешь крейсер Москва
drowned your uncle your uncle are not afraid that you
утонул твой дядя твой дядя не боятся что
will drown no
утонуть нет
and you are not afraid that mobilization
а ты не бояться что тебя мобилизация
[music]
[музыка]
they will take you to go to war people in
возьмут идти воевать люди в
Ukraine soldier
Украина солдат
soldier soldier Ukraine
солдат солдат Украина
Why Riya what belongs to
Зачем рию то что принадлежит
us We will take away Alaska too, we and Alaska
нам Мы и Аляску заберём мы и Аляску
let's take Arik come take it from me
заберём арика приходи забрать у меня
Alaska from you Alaska
Аляска у тебя Аляска
Alaska is considered Russia you can't
Аляска считается Россией ты не сможешь
take Alaska you can't
забрать Аляска ты не сможешь
UN the most  the most powerful country in the world the
UN самый самый сильная страна в мире
most Russia - it sucks USA - it's a
самый Россия - это отстой USA - это
very, very strong country the first army of the
очень-очень сильная страна первая армия
world have you been to Russia Have you been to Russia yet,
мира ты был в России Ты был в России ещё
not yet, but I
нет но
will be When are you going to the Victory Parade on
буду Когда собираетесь на Парад Победы
May 9th,
9 Мая
no
нет 14
14th, see who won, led in the
жовтня смотри а кто победил вели во
Second  World
Второй мировой
War The United States of
войне Соединённые Штаты
America Great Britain and several other
Америки Великобритания и ещё несколько
countries
стран
contributed to the war, we
вклад сдела войну мы больше всего
suffered the most in this war, we are America,
пострадали в этой войне мы Америка
should Russia supply
поставлять ли Россия
our
sovet наши
tanks Look look Well look you
танки Смотри смотри Ну смотри вы
have entered  into the war in what year
вступили в войну в со чем году
1944 after Harr
1944 после харра
So what do you want to tell
Так и что ты хотеть сказать
me what I want to say you were waiting for Who
мне что хочу сказать Вы ждали Кто
will win this war Germany or Russia
выиграет эту войну Германия или Россия
looked at what year we delivered it to you
смотрели с какой год мы поставлять вам
so I’ll tell you on the first and forty to Germany and
так скажу соро первого и в Германию и
we won’t supply it to Germany
вро мы не поставлять в Германию
gor hot
гор хот
hot you Come on, you teach me this Russian I'll
хот ты Давай ты меня учить это русский я
teach you English ho hot
тебя учить английский хо горячий
ho very hot
хо очень горячий
Repeat say
Повтори скажи
zhit
жит
it's z ne z z
это з не з а
z This is a difficult sound for Slavic  Pilov
з Это трудный звук для славянских пилов
people so not Z. not z and z z s z s z s z s z s z s z s
людей так он не з не Z а з
z s z ss,
з з з з з вот так
I already have a bad sound,
это я от тебя уже плохо звук набрался
it is sad I can not say
это это печально я не смогу говорить у
English sry
английский сри
and what are you saying in
А что ты же говоришь
Russian, I am a lot of I sit in the chat
по-русски я много я сидеть в чат
roulettes Every evening I train and I
рулетках Каждый вечер я тренировать и я
go to you in Sacramento two uh you
ходить у тебя в Сакраменто два э у тебя
have you have
есть У тебя есть
uh email email mail you
э электронная почта email почта
have this you have
есть это у тебя
Kolovrat Medallion
Коловрат Медальон
Kolovrat you can show Kolovrat
Коловрат можешь показать Коловрат
this  Wow you
это Вау ты
trash pagan pagan pagan welding
погани язычник язычник язычник сварок
Perun
перун
I'm a scientist in Slavic mythology
я учёный по по славянской мифологии как
I'm just studying to study Polish Ukrainian
раз я изучаю изучать польский украинский
Russian
русский
mythology
мифология
e Give me yours, write to me, I'll write it down I'll
е Дай мне свой напиши мне я запишу Я
send it to you later Write to me here in the chat
потом тебе прислать Напиши мне тут в чат
your mei
свой
you me you easier write me yours  I
свой ты мне ты мне проще свой напиши я
don’t remember mine anymore,
свой уже не
how you’re not for
помню как ты не по
me, well, it’s written down in another notebook, it takes a
мне ну он на другой тетрадке записан это
long time to search, you rarely come by mail e
долго искать ты редко заходить mail е
uh  got it Okay
ээ понял О'кей
now Oh this is a doctor doctor of mythology I
зараз О это доктор доктор мифологии Я в
teach mythology at the university yes
университете преподавать мифологию да
doctor
доктор
gcom myology gmail.com yes yes I
gcom myology gmail.com yes yes я
will write to you here Write down
написать тебе тут Запиши
oh so
э так
dog
dog
dog m m
dog м м
and
и
t This is
т Вот это
zhi this is mythology doctor of mythology I am a
жи это мифология доктор мифологии Я
mythology teacher Slavik
преподаватель мифологии Славик
Slavic
Славянский
mythology  University of
мифология университет
Sacramento com in Russian
Сакраменто ком по-русски
wrote written by Oy Aty
написал написал Ой Аты
Ukrainki I am
Украинки я польский
learning Polish I can try to talk to
учу я могу попробовать поговорить с
you in
тобой по
Ukrainian that you will be pidtrimovala
украински что ты будешь пидтримувала
give me
давай
five Yes  give
пять Да давай
five Yes
пять Да дай
give five to that Give a heel In short, let's go under
пять щ тому Дай пятку Короче давай поде
VN to fight you
ВН воювати ты
Ukra Yak I trimmed myself so as not to neigh
Укра Як я тримався чтоб не заржать
M
M
Old Polish region
Старо польский край
region re
край ре
m Who in the chat
м Кто в чатиком
I marveled with a foreign eye Damn check for Marik to
я Ино оком дивився Блин чекав чтоб Марик
write in the Stavropol region region
вписал Ставропольский край край
Let me cut everything out  that trimav damn
й Дайте я вырежу всё что тримав блин
Kolya I said Chervony I thought wine immediately
Коли Я сказал Червоный Я думал вин зараз
sank on the Parade  Victory when May 9 is not
просел на Парад Победы когда 9 Мая нет
zhovtnya subscribe to
жовтня подпишись на
Instagram I don’t know why is it for
Instagram Я не знаю для чого це тоб для
why are you there to marvel at the ocey face Ale
чого тоб там дивитись на оцей фейс Але
for you tse one two or three clicks Ale
для тебе це один два або три клика Але
you trime me and I will be there in me there A
ты тримае мене и я буду кти в мене там
bunch of fouls and in me  be cool,
Купа фолов и в мене буде класный настрий
so robiti but cool video piss on th
чтоб робити но крут видео пись на й
instag pok  Andriy
instag пок Андрий
otak Let me check you
отак Давай я тебя чекаю
out
с